asics.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy | asicsamerica.com

ASICS America Corporation (the "Company") understands the importance of protecting the privacy of its customers, employees and visitors to this website (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy discloses the Company’s practices relating to collection, use and disclosure of information that you may provide to the Company, including through this Site. Before you submit any personal information to the Company through this Site or otherwise, please thoroughly review this Privacy Policy, and contact us if you have any questions.

### Intended Audience of this Site

This Site is primarily intended for business use by (i) representatives of actual and potential customers interested in learning about the Company or purchasing Company products.

This Site is not intended to attract or be used by children under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent, and the Company will not knowingly collect personal information from such visitors.

### Your Consent

By using this Site, you agree with and accept the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit personal information through this Site, you consent to the collection, disclosure, use and retention of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Collection of Information About You

The Company collects personal information from its customers and prospective customers primarily to assist in meeting their needs for athletic footwear,apparel, and accessories. We collect such information directly from you through this Site, in responses to our specific requests and via e-mail, web input screens and forms, and our newsletter sign-up. The types of personal information we collect includes, but is not limited to, your name, age, gender, street address, and e-mail address. You should carefully limit the personal information you voluntarily provide to strictly that which is necessary for the Company to respond to your inquiry or address your needs for athletic footwear, apparel And accessories.

### Automatic Collection of Information

As you navigate this Site, certain limited information can and may be collected automatically from you without your active involvement, using methods known as cookies, pixel tags/web beacons, and navigational data collection (“Collection Tools”). Some of the information (e.g., type of web browser) does not identify who you are. Other information, such as your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, may identify you indirectly, when supplemented with other commercially available sources of information.

When you visit this Site, we send to your computer one or more cookies, which are small text files containing a string of characters. These cookies uniquely identify your computer to the Site, but do not facilitate the gathering of personal information. We may use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. This information is also used for retargeting, which takes the information collected by your browser’s or device’s cookies to advertise products or services you have interacted with and/or clicked on the Site. These ads will appear on other websites once you leave the Site through the services of, but not limited to, the following: Google Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager, and Google Analytics Demographics Reporting.

Most web browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. NOTE: If you choose to turn off certain Collection Tools, you may not have access to many features that make your experience more efficient, and some of our services and features may not function properly. However, you can still place product orders over the telephone by contacting our Customer Care number at 1-855-233-3120. Note that the Site and our third-party advertising services may not recognize or respond to Do Not Track (DNT) headers from web browsers.

Furthermore, our computer servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information, such as the portions of the Site accessed, the IP address assigned to your computer, the type of browser used by your computer, the date and time of your access to the Site, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your computer.

### Collection, Disclosure, Use and Retention of Information Other Than Employee Data

Except as otherwise stated at the point of collection, we may use your information for improving the content of the Site, customizing this Site to your preferences, communicating information to you and subsequently updating such information, internal marketing and research purposes, and as further specified in this Privacy Policy. We may combine such information with other passively or actively collected information unless we specify otherwise at the point of collection.

The Company may transfer your information, including personally identifiable information, to third parties, including contractors we use to support our business (e.g., marketing services, product retailers, technical support, and financial institutions), in which case we will require such third parties to agree to treat your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy or as you may otherwise have previously consented. We do not share your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you have affirmatively agreed in advance to such a disclosure.

The Company also may transfer such information (i) to our related parent corporation (ASICS Corporation (Kobe, Japan) and other ASICS related corporations around the world (ii) in connection with the sale, assignment or other transfer of the business function of the Company to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such buyer, assignee or transferee to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy; (iii) to protect the rights, property or safety of the Company, its employees or visitors to this Site; or (iv) in compliance with subpoenas or other valid court orders, in response to inquiries and requests from regulatory authorities, in connection with the prevention or detection of fraud, or as otherwise permitted or required by law. In addition, we will make full use of all information acquired through this Site or otherwise that is not identifiable to you.

### Choices for Disclosure and Use of Personal Information

You may choose to prevent the Company from disclosing or using your personal information under certain circumstances ("opt out"). You may opt out of any disclosure or use of your personal information for purposes that are incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected or for which you subsequently gave authorization. Furthermore, even where your personal information is to be disclosed and used in accordance with the stated purposes in this Privacy Policy, you may elect to opt out of such disclosure to and use by a third party that is not acting as an agent of the Company. On the other hand, the Company may disclose your personal information to a third party acting as its agent where this third party subscribes to the Safe Harbor Principles (the "Principles") or agrees in writing to provide at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by the relevant Principles. To opt-out of receiving ads tailored by third party advertising services, please refer to these websites: [Google Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads) and [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). NOTE: You may still see our ads on other websites after opting out of third party tracking, but they will not be tailored using third party tracking technologies associated with the Site.

### Access and Correction

To access your personal information in the possession of the Company and correct inaccuracies of that information in our records, please contact us in the manner specified in the "How to Contact Us" section below. We ask individuals to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed and amended before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests in limited circumstances as permitted by applicable privacy legislation.

### Security

The Company takes reasonable measures to safeguard your personal information against unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification, whether or not in electronic format. We use industry-standard technological precautions, such as Secure Socket Layer technology in an effort to protect your personal information as you transmit it electronically from your computer to this Site and, furthermore, to protect it from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Furthermore, the Company requires that employees and third-party administrators/processors access your personal information only on a "need-to-know" basis.

You should keep in mind that no combination of security measures can ever provide guaranteed protection all the time. We caution you that e-mail may be particularly vulnerable to unauthorized interception, eavesdropping, modification and spoofing, and, therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail. Moreover, where you use passwords, ID numbers or other special access features on this Site, it is your responsibility to safeguard them.

### Enforcement

Any questions, concerns or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy or the Company’s treatment of personal information may be communicated by contacting us through this Site, sending an e-mail message to us at privacy@asicsamerica.com or by writing to us at Privacy Officer, ASICS America Corp., 29 Parker, Suite 100, Irvine California 92618 U.S.A.

When we receive a formal written complaint, our Privacy Officer will contact the author within a reasonable period of time regarding his or her concerns and attempt to resolve these concerns directly with this individual. If a complainant believes that the Company has engaged in possible unfair or deceptive practices and legal or regulatory violations in connection with its privacy obligations, he or she may file a complaint with the Federal Trade Commission through its website http://www.ftc.gov We will cooperate with the U.S. Federal Trade Commission to resolve any complaint regarding the collection, disclosure, use and retention of personal information that cannot be resolved between the Company and the complainant.

The Company has in place procedures for maintaining the confidentiality of personally identifiable information.

### Links to Other Websites

This Site may contain links or references to third-party websites that are not affiliated with the Company. The inclusion of any link does not imply the Company’s endorsement of any other company, its websites, or its products and/or services. Any such linked websites have separate and independent privacy policies which we encourage you to read carefully. Please be aware that the Company has no control over linked third-party websites and, therefore, no responsibility or liability for the manner in which the organizations that operate such websites may collect, disclose, use or otherwise treat your personal information.

### Other Terms

Your use of this Site is subject to our Terms and Conditions of Use.

### How to Contact Us

To correct or update any personal information previously collected by us, please follow instructions at the original point of collection on this Site, send an e-mail message to us at privacy@asicsamerica.com or by writing to us at Privacy Officer, ASICS America Corp., 29 Parker, Suite 100, Irvine California 92618 U.S.A.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will be posted on this Site. Please check back periodically and especially before you provide any personal information to the Company. This Privacy Policy was last updated on February 4, 2009.

## California Privacy Policy

A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he or she has established a business relationship ("California customer") is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. As a general matter, if the business has made such a disclosure of personal information, upon receipt of a request by a California customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom personal information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal information that were disclosed.

However, under the law, a business is not required to provide such lists of information if the business adopts and discloses to the public, in its privacy policy, a policy of not disclosing customer’s personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the business maintains and discloses this policy. Instead, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of personal information and providing a cost free means to exercise that right.

As stated in our Privacy Policy, ASICS America Corporation (the "Company") does not share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you have affirmatively agreed to such a disclosure. If you do request that the Company share your personal information with a third party for that third party’s marketing purposes, we will only share information in connection with that specific purpose. We do not share such information with any third party on a regular or continual basis. To prevent disclosure of your personal information for use in direct marketing by a third party, do not opt in to such use when you provide personally identifiable information on this website.

Please note that whenever you opt in to receive future communications from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party's privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as the Company has no control over how third parties use your information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.

California customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by e-mailing [californiaprivacy@asicsamerica.com](mailto:californiaprivacy@asicsamerica.com). Please note that the Company is only required to respond to one request per California customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this e-mail address.
